http://www.commercebank.com/online-privacy-policy

Skip To Main Content
Log in or select an account:
Related Articles
Commerce Banks Inclusion and Diversity Efforts are Rooted in Our Core Values
How does a bank make a community a better place to live
Commerce Banks Inclusion and Diversity Efforts are Rooted in Our Core Values
Taking Care of Our Team Members During COVID19
Financial considerations for the coronavirus and other emergencies
Online Privacy Policy & Terms of Service
The Commerce Bank Online Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share, and protect information that we collect from United States visitors to our websites.
The Terms of Service apply to Commerce websites, and to any service accessed in connection with a Commerce website.
Commerce Bank uses your email address to advertise our products and services to you through Facebook and Twitter. To have your email address removed from this type of future advertising, use the link below.
Online Privacy Policy [PDF] 1
Terms of Service
Opt Out of Commerce Bank Targeted Advertising on Facebook and Twitter
Disclosures
1 To view or print a PDF file, Adobe Reader® 9.5 or above is recommended. Download the latest version.
About Us
About Us Overview
Get to Know Us
Social Responsibility
Investor Relations
Media Center
Awards & Recognition
Careers
Facebook
You are now leaving the Commerce Bank website.
By clicking the "I Agree" button below, you acknowledge and agree to the following:
You will leave the Commerce Bank website and enter a third party social media/collaboration website. The information shared on Facebook.com is not the responsibility of Commerce Bank and we are not responsible for the content shared between users and participants on the site. Please note that Facebook.com may have its own privacy and security policies which differ from those of Commerce Bank.
Never share your personal information on Facebook.
Twitter
You are now leaving the Commerce Bank website.
By clicking the "I Agree" button below, you acknowledge and agree to the following:
You will leave the Commerce Bank website and enter a third party social media/collaboration website. The information shared on Twitter.com is not the responsibility of Commerce Bank and we are not responsible for the content shared between users and participants on the site. Please note that Twitter.com may have its own privacy and security policies which differ from those of Commerce Bank.
Never share your personal information on Twitter.
LinkedIn
You are now leaving the Commerce Bank website.
By clicking the "I Agree" button below, you acknowledge and agree to the following:
You will leave the Commerce Bank website and enter a third party social media/collaboration website. The information shared on LinkedIn.com is not the responsibility of Commerce Bank and we are not responsible for the content shared between users and participants on the site. Please note that LinkedIn.com may have its own privacy and security policies which differ from those of Commerce Bank.
Never share your personal information on LinkedIn.
Instagram
You are now leaving the Commerce Bank website.
By clicking the "I Agree" button below, you acknowledge and agree to the following:
You will leave the Commerce Bank website and enter a third party social media/collaboration website. The information shared on Instagram.com is not the responsibility of Commerce Bank and we are not responsible for the content shared between users and participants on the site. Please note that Instagram.com may have its own privacy and security policies which differ from those of Commerce Bank.
Never share your personal information on Instagram.
Globe Link and Icon
Privacy Statement | Online Privacy Policy & Terms of Service | En Español
Copyright © 2020 Commerce Bancshares, Inc. All rights reserved. Commerce Bank: Member FDIC.
Close
I Agree
